<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BIGZ Halloween</string>
    <string name="suspect_1">Suspect 1</string>
    <string name="suspect_2">Suspect 2</string>
    <string name="suspect_3">Suspect 3</string>
    <string name="suspect_4">Suspect 4</string>
    <string name="suspect_5">Suspect 5</string>
    <string name="txt_c0"><![CDATA[
<p>Hello, Cryptanalyst.</p>
<p>Let\'s see your information... You\'re <b>Syfer Liste</b>, a top cryptanalyst from England huh... Ever tried to step into a real crime scene?</p>
<p>Anyway, before the crime happened, we intercepted a message from the killer. Perhaps you could check it out? Just go to the <b>electronic database</b>, please NOT confuse it with the paper database. I\'m sure you can find the way.</p>
<p>To <b>access the database</b>, just use your name. No capitals or space needed.</p>
--- C.S.I.B Director, Athello Apona]]></string>
    <string name="txt_hidden_c1">
        <![CDATA[Welcome to the Electronic Database, Listen. I heard from Apona that you’re going to have to access the <b>Sigil Killer’s message</b>? Well, here ya go! We’ve deciphered pretty much all of it, but we are stuck on the <b>second word</b>. It would be wonderful if you could go to the analysis lab in the first building here and talk to the specialist about it. I think he was <b>Miro Jurisic</b>? Remember, it’s not the room at the last end of the hallway. Anyways, Good luck. <p></p>--- C.S.I.B. Computer Forensic Department Director, Aring Tulan]]>
    </string>
    <string name="txt_c1_puzzle">
        <![CDATA[
<p>Puzzle 1:</p>
<p>[Hint: The two lines below shows exactly the <strong>same information</strong>, try to find out the <strong>relationship</strong> between the letters and find what is the second word of the sentence.]</p>
<p>Aol mpuhs wohzl vm aol wshu ohz illu mpupzolk. Vusf aptl hdhpaz.</p>
<p>Progress in decoding:</p>
The ????? phase of the plan has been finished. Only time awaits
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="txt_hidden_c2">
        <![CDATA[
<p>Doing a good job so far, Liste. Apparently there is some kind of plan that is maybe related to the case. Intriguing&hellip; I wonder if the cases before today also links towards the so-called plan&hellip; I&rsquo;ll see if someone knows. I&rsquo;ll possibly call Dr. Qiu if that&rsquo;s the case&hellip; Anyway, now we know that there&rsquo;s a <strong>plan</strong> of some sort, and it&rsquo;s near <strong>finished</strong>. Pretty bad news&hellip; Our investigators tracked the IP address from the <strong>sender</strong> from the last address and found a database. We&rsquo;re working on it, but it seems like there&rsquo;s one document that is heavily encrypted. Can you help? Just meet us at the discussion room <strong>above the lab</strong> once you&rsquo;re done. I think the <strong>last digits</strong> of the room ends in a 1. When your there, send me the <strong>decrypted file&rsquo;s decrypted name</strong> that you&rsquo;ve got.</p>
--- C.S.I.B Computer Forensic Department Director, Tulan
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="txt_c2_puzzle">
        <![CDATA[
<p>[The truth will be shown when the <strong>beginning is the end</strong>]</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>OPENING evhhvo.txt&hellip;</p>
Gsv kozm uli yfrowrmt z evhhvo rh xlnrmt gl zm vmw. Hllm tolib droo wvhxvmw.
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="txt_hidden_c3">
        <![CDATA[
<p>Hmm. A <strong>&ldquo;</strong><strong>vessel</strong><strong>&rdquo;</strong> huh&hellip; A vessel usually refers to some kind of hollowed <strong>containers</strong>---a box, if you will, but to contain something. What are they trying to contain? What is this <strong>person</strong>...or the<strong> group</strong> trying to do?</p>
<p>I have a feeling that the <strong>&ldquo;</strong><strong>vessel</strong><strong>&rdquo;</strong> isn&rsquo;t only just a box made out of wood and stuff. We&rsquo;ve found a page from an encrypted diary here, but we don&rsquo;t have the time to figure every word out. That&rsquo;ll be your next mission. Just go to one of the labs in the building once you&rsquo;ve figured out the <strong>highlighted word</strong>. You know, the one with <strong>ohmmeters and ammeters</strong> inside&hellip; I think it also functions as a classroom for new recruits. Remember, it&rsquo;s not the room at the <strong>last end</strong> of the hallway.</p>
--- C.S.I.B Computer Forensic Department Director, Tulan
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="txt_c3_puzzle">
        <![CDATA[
<p>PUZZLE 3:</p>
<p>[<strong>COORDINATES</strong>: (y,x),(y,x),(y,x),(y,x),(y,x),(y,x),(y,x)&hellip;]</p>
422215441541411526452326261215311114153316422215<strong>41153241333651</strong>3336211132413316422215221536154223134115511541163336442341233332151136411633362215113623322131334342221633364134151125233221262331124116333616151526233221113214323341151633364131152626233221
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="txt_hidden_c4">
        <![CDATA[
<p>Oh. Oh no. This is terrifying. The <strong>vessel </strong>is made out of <strong>sensory organs</strong>&hellip; In a weird way this actually make sense!</p>
<p>Let me explain. You know about the <strong>serial murder case</strong> that happened in the past few days, yeah? They are all <strong>missing out an organ</strong>. The first one missed both her eyes. The second one missed both his ears. The third one, her nose. The fourth one, his lips. The fifth one&hellip; her limbs. The related senses are also depicted in the <strong>sigil</strong>!</p>
<p>This must be related to the senses somehow too. There might be a <strong>&ldquo;sixth sense&rdquo;</strong> somehow&hellip; I&rsquo;ll have to talk to Dr. Spitz somehow. In the meantime, we&rsquo;ve hacked into the mainframe of the database and saw a map. We figured that this might be related to the <strong>first crime scene</strong>---yes, the first few bodies are all <strong>moved</strong> from somewhere. Can you find that place? Here is the map for you if you want to, try to trace the <strong>path</strong> of the delegates, trust your <strong>instinct</strong> and <strong>letters</strong> will be there. Go to that place and input the same word.</p>
--- C.S.I.B Computer Forensic Department Director, Tulan
]]>
    </string>
    <string name="txt_c4_puzzle">
        <![CDATA[
<p>Puzzle 4:</p>
<p>New World Order Ceremonial Parade:</p>
<p>Path of Delegate Horatio:</p>
<p>Day 1: Krutardia, Roclif, Chevouerdon, Panolian</p>
<p>Day 2: Bybia, Tampula</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Path of Delegate Osleton:</p>
<p>Day 3: Bjernes, Roclif, Loskor, Moriatum</p>
<p>Day 4: Makhusia, Burnorumia, Hofjorvo, Minato, Migterrian</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Path of Delegate Hyed:</p>
<p>Day 5: Onainsia, Moriatum, Bybia, Migterrian</p>
<p>Day 6: Mostian, Jistui, Isogu, Porvikemia, Mostian</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Path of Delegate Samson:</p>
<p>Day 7: Bjernes, Roclif, Loskor, Moriatum</p>
Day 8: Makhusia, Burnorumia, Hofjorvo, Minato, Migterrian
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="txt_hidden_c5">
        <![CDATA[
<p>You are almost there, Liste. Good job on finding the first crime scene---you&rsquo;ve been a great help, and we also learnt a lot about the <strong>Vessel</strong>, whatever it is. The last thing you need to do is to find the <strong>suspect</strong>. Unfortunately, the camera data was corrupted&hellip; Luckily, we have an AI that can mostly untangle the data. It can only do so much though---you&rsquo;ll need to do the rest.</p>
<p>Good luck. Report back to the <strong>crime scene</strong> of the sixth victim once you know who is the suspect.</p>
<p>Keep in mind that no analyst knows all the information---sometimes you just have to do what you can.</p>
<p>Remember the words: SEEING IS BELIEVING.</p>
<p>Goodbye for now,</p>
--- C.S.I.B Computer Forensic Department Director, Tulan
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="txt_c5_puzzle">
        <![CDATA[
<p>Puzzle 5:</p>
<p>[(A,B) = (word, letter)</p>
<p>(password sequence, location)]</p>
<p>DATA INFLUX. DATA INFLUX. ALL <strong>DATA SENT </strong><strong>FROM PREVIOUS CONNECTIONS</strong> HAS BEEN MIXED. REPEAT. DATA TNFLUX. ALL INPUT HAS BEEN MIXED.</p>
14 ? ? 42 ? 35 36 14 ? 12 46
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="txt_a0">
        <![CDATA[
<p>Hello, Agent.</p>
<p>Welcome again, Agent Iskat Videlya. I assume your vacation back home in St. Petersburg was well? Anyway, time to work. You saw the crime scene---you know the drill. As a field agent, you need to find <strong><strong>witnesses</strong></strong>&nbsp;and <strong><strong>possible suspects</strong></strong>. I am looking forward to your success. Go to the building near the crime scene first---the <strong><strong>actors and actresses were rehearsing</strong></strong>. Perhaps they have some information?</p>
<p>To <strong><strong>access the database</strong></strong>, just use your name. No capitals or space needed.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
--- C.S.I.B Leader, Athello Apona
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="txt_hidden_a1">
        <![CDATA[
<p>Agent Videlya, nice to see you again.</p>
<p>We&rsquo;ve received a report that some actors in the theatre has spotted a strange man running off the crime scene. Seeing that the camera data got corrupted somehow, the only thing that we can rely on is the <strong><strong>witnesses</strong></strong>&nbsp;of the actors. However, their memories are fuzzy&hellip; See if you can find out the <strong><strong>characteristics</strong></strong>&nbsp;that the suspect have. We&rsquo;ve narrowed down to these <strong><strong>8 keywords</strong></strong>: Jewelry, Gemstone, Glasses, Red hair, Yellow watch, Green hat, tattoo.</p>
<p>Once you know the accessories they talked about, go to the <strong><strong>financial tracking database</strong></strong>&nbsp;so that we can search for the <strong><strong>transaction data</strong></strong>&nbsp;for the accessories. I remember that the person governing this is <strong><strong>Mr. Schneider</strong></strong>. See if you can find him in his room.</p>
--- C.S.I.B Information Department Head, Sunya Sunasapta
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="txt_a1_puzzle">
        <![CDATA[
<p>Puzzle;1:</p>
<p>[Each Witness provides one statement, only one of them are true, try to find out what the suspect is <strong><strong>wearing.</strong></strong>]</p>
<p><br />Witness A: The suspect do not have some of the traits.</p>
<p>Witness B: the Suspect show all of the traits.</p>
<p>Witness C: The suspect did not wear gemstones</p>
Witness D: The suspect wears a green hat.
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="txt_hidden_a2">
        <![CDATA[
<p>Is this thing on?</p>
<p>Hey Agent Videlya. I&rsquo;m currently busy right now, so I suppose you&rsquo;ll have to use the database on your own then. From what Sunasapta told me just now, it seems like the suspect purchased a lot of <strong><strong>gemstones</strong></strong>?</p>
<p>This is weird. From what I can see, there is a spike in purchasing things that are directly linked to the <strong><strong>five senses</strong></strong>&hellip; For what I can find, here are the gems that are being purchased by a <strong><strong>suspicious credit card</strong></strong>---I think it&rsquo;s that <strong><strong>man</strong></strong>. Although, there seems to be a lot of decoy purchases. Can you help find out which <strong><strong>city</strong></strong>&nbsp;the <strong><strong>real purchases</strong></strong>&nbsp;are from? I have a feeling that that might be where our murderer comes from.</p>
<p>Good luck! Once you get there, go to the <strong><strong>surveillance room</strong></strong>&nbsp;and message Sunasapta from there. It&rsquo;s in the <strong><strong>third building</strong></strong>, and it&rsquo;s being <strong><strong>disguised</strong></strong>&nbsp;as an entertainment room. The spears for weapons are even disguised as poles there! CSIB really did a good job on secrecy.</p>
You might find <strong><strong>three documents</strong></strong>&nbsp;around this room useful.
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="txt_a2_puzzle">
        <![CDATA[
<p>Puzzle 2:</p>
<p>[Intercepted courtesy of Liste:</p>
&ldquo;Remember to make your transactions in two places at the same time to confuse the police. All of the transactions will be send <strong><strong>t</strong></strong><strong><strong>hrough</strong></strong>&nbsp;the headquarters <strong><strong>directly</strong></strong>,&nbsp;then to a location where any other transactions occurred at the <strong><strong>same time</strong></strong>.&rdquo;]
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="txt_p0">
        <![CDATA[
<p>Hello, Researcher.</p>
<p>Welcome to China on behalf of the CSIB, Dr. Sigma Kurashiki. As a recommended researcher from the SCP Foundation Japanese branch, I trust you have a lot of experience on paranormal activities. We are suspecting that there are some strange activities involved---especially in one of the rooms here. It&rsquo;s a <strong><strong>strange room</strong></strong>---there&rsquo;s not a lot of it inside, only a <strong><strong>piano</strong></strong>, but lately something\'s happening there. You should start there first.</p>
<p>To <strong><strong>access the database</strong></strong>, just use your name. No capitals or space needed.</p>
--- C.S.I.B Leader, Athello Apona
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="txt_hidden_p1">
        <![CDATA[
<p>Hello, Kurashiki. I am now talking to you through a transmitter, though I&rsquo;m afraid the connection is bad, and I might not be able to transmit <strong>real-time audio</strong>&nbsp;communications to you. So listen well.</p>
<p>There has been some strange occurrences before the estimated time of death of the victim. We have the data now---I&rsquo;ll send it to you. It seems like it is a <strong><strong>symbol</strong></strong>---though we don&rsquo;t know what it means. However, there should be some<strong><strong>&nbsp;transcription and translation notes</strong></strong>&nbsp;in your room now somewhere. Try to find enough information to decipher the symbol&rsquo;s meaning. Once you know what it is, go to the <strong><strong>symbol room</strong></strong>---it&rsquo;s at your floor. Strangely, there are some <strong><strong>kitchen utensils</strong></strong>&nbsp;in that room alongside with <strong><strong>graph papers</strong></strong>.</p>
Good luck. Sinclair out.
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="txt_hidden_p2">
        <![CDATA[
<p>Well this is alarming. A <strong>symbol of death</strong>&hellip; According to my resources, they belong to a set of symbols called the <strong>Greco</strong>, as I call them, because of the supposedly <strong>link to Greek letters</strong>. They are simple, but using different <strong>frequencies of light</strong>&nbsp;we can actually observe a <strong>pattern</strong>. They seem to...fit into another. I&rsquo;ve sent you the analysis of the symbol you just translated. There should be<strong>&nbsp;9 more</strong>&nbsp;hidden around this room. Remember that the Grecos are linked to Greek letters? Well, there seemed to be <strong>2</strong>&nbsp;in this set of symbols. Try to find them and send the <strong>two</strong><strong>&rsquo;</strong><strong>s English name without spaces</strong>&nbsp;to me. I&rsquo;ll be waiting in the <strong>stenography room</strong>. The room is governed by Mrs. Abbe-Dowd and filled with literature books. </p>
---SCP Foundation Head of Occult Studies and Thaumatology Division, Sinclair
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="txt_hidden_p3">
        <![CDATA[
<p>This is alarming. Alpha and Omega mean &ldquo;<strong>create</strong>&rdquo; and &ldquo;<strong>destroy</strong>&rdquo;, and is common in <strong>rituals</strong>. And those are not good rituals, trust me. Almost all of them has a purpose of destroying the world and recreating them---hence &ldquo;Create&rdquo; and &ldquo;Destroy&rdquo;. I need more info, though---seems like analyzing the meaning &ldquo;Create&rdquo; and &ldquo;Destroy&rdquo; might work. There should be a <strong>wheel of names</strong>&nbsp;in the room---try to decipher the <strong>god</strong><strong>&rsquo;</strong><strong>s name</strong>&nbsp;using it. There should be <strong>12 letters</strong>&nbsp;for your result. Once you are done, send it to me at the <strong>mythology research department</strong>. Lately they&rsquo;ve been researching <strong>Greco-Roman mythology </strong>and they are learning the language of the <strong>Ancient Romans</strong>&nbsp;now. It&rsquo;s on the <strong>5th floor</strong>---I&rsquo;m sure you can find it.</p>
---SCP Foundation Head of Occult Studies and Thaumatology Division, Sinclair
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="txt_hidden_p4">
        <![CDATA[
<p>&hellip;.Shoot.</p>
<p>This is bad. Tezcatlipoca is the <strong>god of darkness</strong> in <strong>Aztec</strong>. There is only one cult that I know of that worships Tezcatlipoca---and they are definitely <strong>not the suspect</strong>. There are benevolent and they have alibis. I might try to contact with them to figure something out&hellip;</p>
<p>In the meantime, there is an <strong>obscure worship ritual </strong>surrounding a <strong>single word</strong>---but I can&rsquo;t seem to find it. I&rsquo;ve discovered a <strong>video</strong> of that <strong>ritual</strong>, though---I&rsquo;ve left some camera feeds, annotated with movement lines. Try to see if you can figure it out.</p>
<p>Once you&rsquo;re done, go to the <strong>signal tracking room</strong>. It is the room directly <strong>2 floors beneath</strong> you---and then go <strong>left 1 room</strong>. I think the director there is <strong>Ms. Haley Brill</strong>&hellip;</p>
<p>Good luck,</p>
---SCP Foundation Head of Occult Studies and Thaumatology Division, Sinclair
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="txt_hidden_p5">
        <![CDATA[
<p>Good job. So, <strong>imitation</strong> huh&hellip;. I think I got it. I&rsquo;ve talked to the Bishop of the God of Tez, the benevolent one I told you about earlier. Adding with your information, I think I can track the <strong>suspect&rsquo;s signal</strong>!</p>
<p>Although&hellip; the signal is <strong>jumbled</strong>. Very<strong> jumbled</strong>. You&rsquo;ll have to figure this one out. Only one step and you&rsquo;ll find out the suspect. I&rsquo;ll send the data to you&hellip; Good luck.</p>
Remember the words:<strong> SENSES</strong> LIE SOMETIMES FOR OUR SAKE.
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="txt_h0">
        <![CDATA[
<p>Hello, Researcher.</p>
<p>Been expecting you here, Dr. Qiu. You are the go-to researcher in the Guangzhou faction here, anyway. We have been setting up a <strong>remote database</strong> in the<strong> third building </strong>for you here; unfortunately, due to cybersecurity concerns they are all in <strong>paper forms</strong>, We could only allow a <strong>couple computers</strong> there. Perhaps you could go take a look?</p>
<p>To <strong>access the database</strong>, just use your name. No capitals or space needed.</p>
--- C.S.I.B Leader, XXX
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="txt_hidden_h1">
        <![CDATA[
<p>Hey Dr. Qiu,</p>
<p>Welcome back to C.S.I.B! Let&rsquo;s get to work, shall we? We&rsquo;ve noticed some <strong>unique commonalities</strong> in the victim and the five cases before, and Dr. Spitz is currently working on it. However, he has sent you a preliminary corpse report. I&rsquo;ve also noticed that there is something <strong>peculiar but similar</strong> with these cases, the killer is doing something is not normal even for a murderer&hellip; Perhaps you could go look into the database? Here are the documents you might need. Once you noticed the strange actions of the killer, go to the lounge of the history department. I think it&rsquo;s on the <strong>first building</strong>, though you&rsquo;ll have to look for it yourself. I heard that a certain <strong>Ms. Settle</strong> is currently in charge of the lounge. Send me an email on what the killer did that might be strange once you&rsquo;re there.</p>
C.S.I.B Historical Database Department Head, ABC.
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="txt_h1_puzzle">
        <![CDATA[
<p>[Possible answers for the strangeness of these cases:</p>
<p><strong>Cause of death, age, estimate time of death, anatomy, discovered place</strong>.]</p>
Here are the victims portfolio created by the forensic scientist.
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="txt_hidden_h2">
        <![CDATA[
<p>So the commonalities are that they all have one of their body parts removed, huh&hellip; And it seems like that they are all <strong>sensory organs</strong>. Hmmm&hellip; I can&rsquo;t help but shake the feeling that something like that also happened in the past, the researchers also found that there is some weird symbols embedded on every victims neck, they looks pretty familiar&hellip; Perhaps these documents can help? Also, I will send you the updated examination on the symbols. I recall that there is a certain <strong>civilization</strong> that likes such bloodshed. Go to the room <strong>2 floors directly above</strong> this room---that&rsquo;s our <strong>occult collection</strong>, if you do remember. Text me the civilization once you&rsquo;re there.</p>
C.S.I.B Historical Database Department Head, ABC.
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="txt_h2_puzzle">
        <![CDATA[
<p>Updated anatomy:</p>
<p>[The document you found was a description of the symbols, they are known to be related to several letters, and the <strong>actual letter</strong> in this case should be related to the <strong>number of symbols</strong> found on the victim, the name of the <strong>civilization </strong>is probably some combination of the these letters. Try to combine them in a <strong>chronological order</strong>.]</p>
<p>Victim 1: one symbol A was found on the victim&rsquo;s neck.</p>
<p>Victim 2: two symbol B was found on the victim&rsquo;s neck.</p>
<p>Victim 3: one symbol D was found on the victim&rsquo;s body.</p>
<p>Victim 4: four symbol C was found on the victim&rsquo;s body.</p>
Victim 5: three symbol E was found on the victim&rsquo;s body.
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="txt_hidden_h3">
        <![CDATA[
<p>Hey. Sorry, I don&rsquo;t really have enough time to text you a new message, but yeah, I received yours. The <strong>Aztec civilization</strong>, huh&hellip; Wonder if there&rsquo;s anything related to this case. I have a bad feeling about this&hellip; There are known <strong>neo-Aztec cults</strong> nowadays as well. A few of them are harmless, but most of them&hellip; We&rsquo;ve lost a great number of our recruits <strong>fighting</strong> them just last year. Something must be related&hellip;</p>
<p>Try to find something---everything is in this room that you are now in. I&rsquo;ll send some info as well. Go to the smaller-scale paper database in the third building once you&rsquo;re finished researching. Remember everything you read here.</p>
---C.S.I.B Historical Database Department Head, ABC.
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="txt_h3_puzzle">
        <![CDATA[

        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="txt_hidden_h4">
        <![CDATA[
<p>Welcome to the top secret database, Dr. Qiu.</p>
<p>That is a lot of information thrown at you, isn&rsquo;t it? Well, that&rsquo;s for a reason---</p>
<p>According to your research that you just did, we strongly suspect that a <strong>neo-Aztec cult</strong> is at fault here.</p>
<p>Here are some files we found from Aztec ruins. These are the maximum that we can do. Try to figure out the <strong>headquarters </strong>of this cult. Then head to the room beside the <strong>electronic database</strong>. It&rsquo;s to the <strong>left.</strong></p>
<p>Good luck. Text me the <strong>location of the headquaters</strong> once you get there.</p>
---C.S.I.B Historical Database Department Head, ABC.
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="txt_h4_puzzle">
        <![CDATA[
<p>[Somethings <strong>wrong</strong> with the text below, the whole text looks weird, try to <strong>correct</strong> the text and the <strong>location of the headquarters</strong> should be hiding in the text you <strong>deleted</strong>.]</p>
&ldquo;To give ligght, they needed a god to becoume the sun and the Black Tezcatlipoca was chosaen, but either becanuse he had lost a legg or because he was god of the night, he only managed to become half a sun. Tzhe world continued on in this way for some time, but a sibling rivalry grew betweenh Quetzalcoatl and his brother the mighty sun, who Quetzalcoatl knoocked from the sky with a stone club. With nou sun, the world was totally black and in his anger, Tezcatlipoca commanded his jaguars to eat all the people.&rdquo;
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="txt_hidden_h5">
        <![CDATA[
<p>Great job, Dr. Qiu. Wow, we are right on the <strong>enemy</strong><strong>&rsquo;</strong><strong>s territory</strong>&nbsp;now. I would have never thought that their headquarters was right here.</p>
<p>And just in time, too. Tulan, our computer forensic specialist, just detected a <strong><strong>hack in our database</strong></strong>. Something tells me that whoever has done the hacking is the suspect. No one should have access to the files except for the CSIB.</p>
<p>I will now transmit the data gathered by the forensic team. However, the <strong><strong>data is corrupted</strong></strong>. Try your best to figure out the <strong><strong>IP address</strong></strong>&nbsp;of the thing. This should lead you to the suspect.</p>
<p>Return to the crime scene once done.</p>
<p>Remember the words: <strong><strong>THE INFORMATION PRODUCER.</strong></strong></p>
--- C.S.I.B Historical Database Department Head, Khala.
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="txt_h5_puzzle">
        <![CDATA[
<p>Puzzle&nbsp;5:</p>
<p>[POSSIBLE LOCATION KEY OF LOCATION ID: LENGTH OF FIRST PASSCODE, LENGTH OF SECOND PASSCODE, NOW HOLY NUMBER,LENGTH OF LAST PASSCODE, then, CYCLE THROUGH till the end of the data.]</p>
<p>Encrypted Location ID: 3734628253916374392163</p>
DJWOCKAEIDMCYTCAIEKCNDOCKELQAUCJEKSUAWNXHM***data corrupted****
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="txt_hidden_a3">
        <![CDATA[
<p>Agent, I trust you finished the task assigned by Mr. Schneider? Good, good&hellip; Now we know that the suspect is likely <strong>Parisian</strong>. Great job.</p>
<p>There is still one more extra clue before we can recreate a 2D model of the suspect&rsquo;s face---yes, we can do that. All we have to do is to find the <strong><strong>first crime scene location</strong></strong>.</p>
<p>You should know this by now, but there are strong evidence that the victim was <strong><strong>brought into </strong></strong>one particular place <strong><strong>before death</strong></strong>. Luckily, although the surveillance camera is corrupted, the <strong><strong>audio system</strong></strong>&nbsp;still works&hellip; Sort of. Look, our computer specialists are working on it, but I trust in your abilities to find out the <strong><strong>first </strong></strong><strong><strong>&ldquo;</strong></strong><strong><strong>crime scene</strong></strong><strong><strong>&rdquo;</strong></strong>. Once you find it, go to the <strong><strong>portrait room</strong></strong>&nbsp;just <strong><strong>upstairs</strong></strong>&nbsp;to send me a message.</p>
--- C.S.I.B Information Department Head, &nbsp;Sunasapta
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="txt_a3_puzzle">
        <![CDATA[

        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="txt_hidden_a4">
        <![CDATA[
<p>The monologue of this guy is&hellip;. interesting. Best to keep that on your mind, agent. Anyways, according to your data, we&rsquo;ve reconstructed a 2D model of the <strong>suspect</strong><strong>&rsquo;</strong><strong>s</strong>&nbsp;face. It&rsquo;s not perfect though, and we&rsquo;ve limited the suspects to around 5 people. Their files are shown in here. Try to <strong>match </strong>what you know to see who is most likely the culprit. Our forces are surrounding the school, so you just have to get to the <strong>interrogation room</strong>&nbsp;in the <strong>rooms</strong>&nbsp;inside to the <strong>paper databases</strong>&nbsp;and send us the <strong>last name</strong>&nbsp;of the suspect there. I have a feeling things are not that simple&hellip;</p>
--- C.S.I.B Information Department Head, &nbsp;Sunasapta
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="txt_a4_puzzle">
        <![CDATA[
<p>Puzzle 4:</p>
<p>2DELPHI TESTING DATA --- FOR REFERENCE ONLY:</p>
<p>Input: Red hair, black eyes, 20-50 yrs</p>
<p>&nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Output: #H100 #E111 ##25</p>
<p>Input: Yellow hair, green eyes, 10-20yrs</p>
<p>&nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Output: #H010 #E010 ##12</p>
<p>Input: Purple hair, red eyes, 40-50 yrs</p>
<p>&nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Output: #H101 #E100 ##45</p>
<p>Input: Green hair, purple eyes, 20-40 yrs</p>
<p>&nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Output: #H110 #E101 ##24</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;Outputting results&hellip;</p>
<p>Known attributes of 2D Face model:</p>
#H000 #E001 ##34
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="txt_hidden_a5">
        <![CDATA[
<p>Great job, Agent Videlya!</p>
<p>I think you got it right! However, I don&rsquo;t think this is the end. We&rsquo;re interrogating the suspect now, and he seemed to point out that there was a <strong><strong>major boss</strong></strong>&nbsp;behind all this. We might be onto something.</p>
<p>Can you make sense of the interrogation? I&rsquo;ve sent the video and the <strong><strong>transcript</strong></strong>&nbsp;of the interrogation. See if you can figure out the boss&rsquo;s <strong><strong>real name</strong></strong>. Go back to the <strong><strong>corpse at the track field</strong></strong>&nbsp;once you are done.</p>
<p>Remember the words: <strong><strong>SOUND IS THE VESSEL OF INFO</strong></strong>.</p>
<p>Goodbye for now,</p>
--- C.S.I.B Information Department Head, &nbsp;Sunasapta
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="txt_a5_puzzle">
        <![CDATA[
<p>Puzzle 5:</p>
<p>Interrogator: Mr. Falloson.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Falloson: ...What?</p>
<p>I: You have been charged with assisted murder, and we have reason to believe that someone is ordering you to do this. Who?</p>
<p>F: ...Why do I need to tell you?</p>
<p>I: Do you not realize the situation you are it?</p>
<p>F: Situation? Ha! Dude, I expected that you&rsquo;ll catch me this time, y&rsquo;know? I&rsquo;m just a decoy. Looks like CSIB are really just a bunch of weakings.</p>
<p>I: Sorry, could you say that again?</p>
<p>F: I SAID, you guys are a bunch of WEAKLINGS! I bet even if I give you hints, you won&rsquo;t be able to tell who the boss is. Do you know his last name and mine rhymes?</p>
<p>I: Okay&hellip;</p>
<p>F: And since I&rsquo;m soooo generous, I&rsquo;ll give you some more hints! If your intel is even slightly capable, you would&rsquo;ve known that his last name has the same amount of letters as [DATA CORRUPTED. POSSIBLE MATCH: THIRD PASS] and his first name has the same numbers of letters as a red [DATA CORRUPTED. POSSIBLE MATCH: FIRST PASS]!</p>
<p>I: Thank you for the information.</p>
<p>F: I bet you can&rsquo;t do anything about it still, huh? Even if I told you if [DATA CORRUPTED: POSSIBLE MATCH: SECOND PASS] was his middle name his name will have a syllable count of 1, 2, 3, you guys won&rsquo;t be able to find him!</p>
<p>I: ...</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
(... is intentional.)
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="txt_f0">
        <![CDATA[
<p>Hello, Scientist.</p>
<p>Thank you for coming to China on such short notice from your base lab in Germany, Dr. Ziel Spitz. The kit has been prepared for you, and the lab has also been set up for your usage. According to primary investigation, there are no noticeable <strong><strong>external injuries</strong></strong>, so we suspect that it was <strong><strong>poison</strong></strong>. I suggest you go to the <strong><strong>restaurant</strong></strong>&nbsp;nearby and collect some samples of the <strong><strong>food</strong></strong>&nbsp;to test whether or not the<strong><strong>&nbsp;food</strong></strong>&nbsp;has been poisoned. Good luck.</p>
<p>To <strong><strong>access the database</strong></strong>, just use your name. No capitals or space needed.</p>
--- C.S.I.B Leader, Athello Apona
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="txt_hidden_f1">
        <![CDATA[
<p>Dr. Spitz, nice to see you again. I trust you have already picked up your kit? Good, good&hellip; Well, here we are, in the canteen. I&rsquo;ve go on and checked the menu&rsquo;s of the <strong>nearest menu</strong>&nbsp;closest to the estimated time of death, and here are the samples. I&rsquo;ve sent the analysis data to you&hellip; See if you can make any sense of these. I&rsquo;ve already ruled out a lot, and what&rsquo;s left are: CYANIDE, STRYCHNINE, ARSENIC, RICIN, HENBANE, CONIINE, or simple NONE.</p>
<p>Once you get the results, meet me in the <strong><strong>lab</strong></strong>. You are a <strong><strong>forensic biological scientist.</strong></strong>&nbsp;You know which <strong><strong>lab</strong></strong>&nbsp;it is.</p>
----CSIB Forensic Department Head, Dee Oksi Ennei
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="txt_f1_puzzle">
        <![CDATA[
<p>Puzzle 1:</p>
<p>[The forensic department have discovered a new reagent that can test the presence of multiple poisons at the same time. Although the reagent are still acting somewhat weird, we decided to use them in order to finish all testings in time. Based on past experience, the data we gain can get provide an answer, but it requires some reasoning&hellip;]</p>
<p>Notice:</p>
<ol>
<li>When only one compound is tested, the reactant will change color if the compound is present.</li>
<li>When two compound are tested together, the reactant will not change if both compound was present.</li>
<li>When three compound are tested together, the reactant will change color if none, one, or two compounds present, or else it will not change.</li>
<li>When four compound are tested together, the reactant will change color if there are none, three, or four compound in the food, else it will not change.</li>
<li>If CYANINE was tested but not found, the result will be the opposite of what is expected.</li>
</ol>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Test 1: test for HENBANE, STRYCHNINE, RICIN. &mdash;&gt; change color.</p>
<p>Test 2: test for CYANINE, ARSENIC, RICIN. &mdash;&gt; no result.</p>
<p>Test 3: test for ARSENIC, CONIINE, HENBANE, STRYCHNINE. &mdash;&gt; change color.</p>
<p>Test 4: test for CONIINE. &mdash;&gt; no reaction.</p>
Test 5: test for STRYCHNINE. &mdash;&gt; no reaction
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="txt_hidden_f2">
        <![CDATA[
<p>You made it! Sorry, I didn&rsquo;t have time to text you, so here&rsquo;s my voice instead. It&rsquo;s strange how the cause of death <strong>isn</strong><strong>&rsquo;</strong><strong>t poison</strong>&nbsp;isn&rsquo;t it? I can&rsquo;t think of another reason why a healthy individual would just die in the middle of the day. I may need further research&hellip; Anyway, here is the <strong>autopsy results</strong>. I&rsquo;ve also dug up the <strong>other cases</strong>&nbsp;from the <strong>Sigil Killer</strong>. Here are their files as well.</p>
<p>See if you can find anything <strong><strong>strange</strong></strong>. I would look at the <strong><strong>abnormality</strong></strong>&nbsp;that doesn&rsquo;t match the cause of death. I await your information in the <strong><strong>analysis lab</strong></strong>. It&rsquo;s <strong><strong>near</strong></strong>&nbsp;you---the room also serves as a <strong><strong>training facility</strong></strong>&nbsp;for forensic biologist interns. I think you know where it is. It&rsquo;s on this floor too.</p>
Good luck. Ennei out.
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="txt_f2_puzzle">
        <![CDATA[
The victims estimate time of death is at 3:00 pm.
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="txt_hidden_f3">
        <![CDATA[
<p>...I suspected that it was the <strong>brain signal</strong>&nbsp;as well. Something tells me that we need further</p>
<br />I&rsquo;ve left a brain scan for you. See if you can figure out which <strong><strong>part</strong></strong>&nbsp;of the brain is behaving strangely. Good luck! I&rsquo;ll be waiting in the <strong><strong>metaphysics lab</strong></strong>. We might have to deal with the metaphysics here. It&rsquo;s on the <strong><strong>same floor</strong></strong>. There&rsquo;s a bunch of <strong><strong>posters</strong></strong>&nbsp;in there about&nbsp;<strong><strong>chess</strong></strong>&nbsp;and stuff. Also the lab is currently focusing on the <strong><strong>philosophy of China</strong></strong>---you know where it is. Good luck!&nbsp;investigation on that, since it looks like the <strong><strong>brain waves</strong></strong>&nbsp;becomes more intense even when the person dies!
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="txt_f3_puzzle">
        <![CDATA[

        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="txt_hidden_f4">
        <![CDATA[
This is truly very weird, what is going on in the <strong>subcortex</strong>&nbsp;of the brain that will cause such <strong>intense activities</strong>? Actually, this reminds me of something&hellip; Something that I read a long time before. Wait a second&hellip; here, found it, I think you might want to read this, the <strong><em>theory of the soul</em></strong>, it is describing symptoms similar to the victim. However, it is probably a little bit too old, some of the data is <strong>buggy</strong>. Try to find the <strong>crucial chemica</strong>l that is used to make the recipe, I think for some reasons it is <strong>completely illegible</strong>. After you decided on your answer, come to the elemental room. It is located in the <strong>first building</strong>, I think there is a lot of <strong>periodic tables</strong>&nbsp;for reference purposes.
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="txt_f4_puzzle">
        <![CDATA[
&ldquo;This&nbsp;is a recipe for those th#t admires the puren^ss of human mind. The pneuma (or soul) was found in the human brain. It is like a light tower guiding every single activities in life. The pneuma can be extracted through several methods, and once it is ext!acted artificially, the human being will loose all abilities to regulate all bodily activities, and the &gt;uman conscious will sink in*o the&nbsp;subcortex layer of the brain. This recipe requires several ingredients, nether wart, #^*&gt;^!, monkey blood, and kitchen dust.&rdquo;
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="txt_hidden_f5">
        <![CDATA[
<p>Okay, <strong>aether</strong>? This information might be crucial to find the Sigil Killer. I&rsquo;ve noticed that their is also a <strong>strange peak</strong>&nbsp;in the access of this file on aether when I found it as well&hellip; No one should be interested in such an absurd recipe expect now. The person who read the file should be related to the <strong>suspect</strong>&nbsp;then. Try to find <strong>her name</strong>&nbsp;using the data on the search engine. Remember, the result did not show<strong>&nbsp;unanimous times</strong>!</p>
[Remember the words: NOSE KNOWS]
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="txt_f5_puzzle">
        <![CDATA[
TIME IS OF THE ESSENCE. FOCUS ON POSITION IN THE ALPHABET
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="txt_help">
        <![CDATA[
<p>To the players:</p>
<p>This game is very simple to operate. It is our version of a scavenger hunt. In order to proceed, you only need to find <strong>two things</strong> in every information we give. One is the <strong>location</strong> where the next QR code is hiding, and the<strong> password</strong> that you need in order to gain access to the information. The location will be hinted in the <strong>text</strong>, try to relate the room that the instructor likes you to go to one of the <strong>rooms in our school.</strong> The password will be the <strong>answer of the puzzle</strong>, and the puzzle will be distinguished from the text in the app.</p>
<p>We are also a role playing game, there are five characters involved in this murder case. The forensic scientist, paranormal scientist, field agent, cryptanalyst, and historian. Feel free to be anyone you want, but once you choose, you <strong>can&rsquo;</strong><strong>t change</strong> you character. If you want some more challenge, we recommend you to choose the paranormal scientist, the puzzles provided is <strong>harder</strong> than the other routes.</p>
<p>Some of the puzzle might be a little difficult, you can discuss with other players that is playing in the same route, or even team up with others and play on the same phone. When you really can&rsquo;t solve the puzzle, always feel free to come to the initial location and ask the <strong>staff</strong> for the <strong>password </strong>by telling them which character you are and which stage you are in. For example, the third stage of the cryptanalyst can be called C-3. However, YOU WILL NOT ENJOY THE PROCESS AS MUCH IF YOU DO SO.</p>
<strong>REMEMBER,</strong> if you found a room that is not accessible, refer back here: If you are asked to go to the ping pong room, look around in the right side hallway of that floor, if it is the library, go to the left entrance to find the code, if it is the discussion room inside the library, go to the right entrance, for the small library, simply look around the left hallway on that floor.&nbsp;
        ]]>
    </string>
</resources>
